clickhype.com 2004-04-23

# ClickHype.com: redefining online advertising

**Privacy Policy :**

ClickHype.com, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website:

Use of Information  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies for affiliate tracking. The cookies containing a referrer's affiliate number will reside on the visitor's computer for three days.  
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user promotional material from some of our partners. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings, however they will remain in our database; see the choice/opt-out section below.  
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information on products and services tailored to their needs. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Contact information from the order form is used to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.  
We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Security  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. ClickHype.com, Inc. has firewalls to protect our database of user addresses from being used or seen by anyone other than ClickHype.com, Inc. Correct/Update This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.  
1.email public@Clickhype.com  
2.call the following telephone number: (205)879-3786

Choice/Opt-Out  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. By opting out, one simply does not check any of our list subscription boxes and unchecks the box that gives us permission to send mail based on occupation, gender, and geographic location.  
This site gives users the further options for removing their personal information from our database to not receive future advertising communications or to no longer receive our service.  
1.You can send email to public@Clickhype.com  
2.You can call the following telephone number: (205)879-3786

Third Party Advertising  
We use MaxWorldwide and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

Children's Guidelines 1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent  
2\. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent  
3\. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent  
4\. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent  
5\. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, the practices ofthis site, or your dealings with this Web site, contact  
ClickHype.com, Inc.  
3 Office Park Circle  
Suite 304  
Birmingham, AL 35223
